A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York Office, 1974-1977; 10; 14.6 Cubic Feet 29 Boxes
  - Sound Recordings, 1974-1977; 10.3; 87 audiocassettes 23 reel-to-reel audiotapes
    - Press Conference, Wellington, New Zealand, April 3, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2.09)
    - NAR Remarks Following Italian Earthquake, May 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2.1)
    - "The Mike Douglas Show", September 28, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2.11)
    - "Who's Who" with Dan Rather, January 18, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2.12)
    - England, NAR Remarks, September 15, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Reel to Reel Tapes
    - Swearing In Ceremony of Mr. Fletcher, February 25, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Tunis, Tunisia, NAR Arrival Statement, March 20, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Tunis, Tunisia, NAR Departure Statement, March 21, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Tunisia and France, NAR Remarks, March 20, 1976 - March 22, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Paris, France, Bicentennial Speech, March 22, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - France, NAR Remarks, March 22, 1976 - March 23, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Malaysia, Singapore, and Australia, NAR Remarks, March 27, 1976 - March 28, 1976, March 31, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Kuala Lumpur Malaysia NAR Remarks, March 27, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Singapore, NAR Speech, March 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sydney, Australia, Speech by Australian Prime Minister Malcom Fraser, March 29, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Australia, NAR Remarks, March 30, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Canberra, Australia, NAR Press Conference, March 30, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Wentworth Hotel, NAR Speech, March 31, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - New Zealand, NAR Remarks, April 2, 1976 - April 3, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - The Commonwealth Club, NAR Speech, May 4, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - The Biltmore Hotel, NAR Speech to the World Affairs Council Luncheon, May 5, 1976; 1 of 2 tapes (Box 12, Folder 0017A)
    - The Biltmore Hotel, NAR Speech to the World Affairs Council Luncheon, May 5, 1976; 2 of 2 tapes (Box 12, Folder 0017B)
    - Representative Conable, Remarks, May 23, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - NAR Address, at the Graduation Ceremonies of the United States Air Force Academy, June 2, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - NAR Address, to the Inter-American Defense College, June 10, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Dedication of Old Senate Chamber (NAR involved), June 16, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Unknown Contents, June 29, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Unknown Contents, n. d. (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Joseph E. Persico Files, 1958-1974; 12; 12 Cubic Feet 28 document boxes
  This series is divided into five subseries: Subseries 1 - New York State Committee to Reelect the President Research Files, 1972 Subseries 2 - Miscellaneous Writings, 1971-1974 Subseries 3 - Pre-Vice Presidential Speeches, 1966-1974 Subseries 4 - Press Releases, 1970-1974 Subseries 5 - Miscellaneous Files, 1958-1974
  This series documents official activities in the execution of Joseph Persico's duties as a member of Nelson A. Rockefeller's staff. The actions, decisions, and exchanges of information or points of view documented here occurred in the course of proposing and implementing policies for the Rockefeller administration, political campaigns, and/or Rockefeller's personal activities. However, unless a document is specifically addressed to or from Nelson Rockefeller, or is referred to in a document addressed to him, it should not be assumed he saw the document or was aware of its existence or substance. Furthermore, researchers should bear in mind that staff files may contain documents or drafts addressed to Rockefeller that were never shown to him.
  This series focuses on Joseph E. Persico's service as the chief speech writer for Nelson A. Rockefeller during his two last terms as Governor of New York (1967-1973) and during his service as Vice President of the United States (1974-1977). This collection contains the speeches and press releases that Persico wrote in this capacity. His personal papers and writings are at the New York State Archives in Albany.
  Most of this series is made up of speech files. They contain one or more different versions of each speech: drafts, reading copies, transcripts, or press releases. Drafts and reading copies are likely to include Governor Rockefeller's handwritten changes and notations. Some files contain memos, schedules, or background information on the event at which the speech was given.
  Biographical / Historical
  Joseph E. Persico was born in Gloversville, New York, on July 19, 1930. He graduated from the State University of New York at Albany in 1952 with a B.A. in both English and political science. He then served in the U.S. Navy for three years as a Lt. Junior Grade aboard a minesweeper and at NATO headquarters in Naples, Italy. Returning to the United States in 1954, he matriculated at Columbia University for his graduate work. He received a Ph.D. from the State University of New York at Albany in 1966.
  He began his writing career in 1956, serving New York Governor Averill Harriman. In 1959, he became a Foreign Service Officer for the U.S. Information Agency (USIA) in Brazil, Argentina, and Washington, DC. Between 1963 and 1966, he served as executive assistant to New York Health Commissioner Hollis Ingraham.
  From 1966 to 1974, Persico was Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller's chief speech writer and remained in that position during Rockefeller's vice presidency.
  Persico's first book, published in 1977, was "My Enemy, My Brother," a history of the Battle of Gettysburg. In 1982, Persico published a biography of Nelson Rockefeller, "The Imperial Rockefeller." More recently, Persico collaborated with Colin Powell on his biography and wrote a book on Franklin Roosevelt, "Roosevelt's Secret War: FDR and World War II Espionage."
  - New York State Committee to Reelect the President Research Files, 1972; 12.1; 2 Cubic Feet
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by state.
    These files contain statistical data and factual information for each U.S. state, including facts on population, polls, state organizations, industry, and key individuals in state governments. These statistics and facts were used by the Committee to Reelect the President research staff based in New York.
    - Alabama (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alaska (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Arizona (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - California (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Colorado (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Delaware (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Florida (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Georgia (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Hawaii (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Idaho (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Illinois (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Indiana (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Iowa (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Kentucky (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Louisiana (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Maine (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Maryland (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Michigan (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Minnesota (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Mississippi (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Missouri (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Montana (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Nebraska (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Nevada (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - New Hampshire (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - New Jersey (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - New Mexico (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - North Dakota (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Ohio (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Oklahoma (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Oregon (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Rhode Island (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - South Carolina (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - South Dakota (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tennesee (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Texas (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Utah (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Vermont (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Virginia (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - West Virginia (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Washington (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Wisconsin (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Writings, 1972-1974; 12.2; 0.5 Cubic Feet
    This subseries contains miscellaneous speeches and transcribed recorded presentations that Governor Rockefeller gave at various functions and locations. The speeches appear in other parts of this collection but were grouped as miscellaneous writings for no specific reason.
    - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Pre-Vice Presidential Speeches, 1966-1974; 12.3; 6.4 Cubic Feet
    This subseries is composed of the speeches written by Joseph Persico for Governor Rockefeller during his third and fourth gubernatorial terms. It also includes speeches written during Rockefeller's first congressional confirmation hearing for U.S. Vice President.
    - January 1966 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - February 1966 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - March 1966 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - April 1966 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - May 1966 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - June 1966 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - July 1966 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - August 1966 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - September 1966 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - October 1-17, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - October 18-30, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - November 1966 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - December 1966 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - January 1967 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - February 1967 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - March 1967 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - April 1967 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - May 1967 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - June 1967 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - July 1967 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - August 1967 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - September 1967 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - October 1967 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - November 1967 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - December 1967 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - January 1968 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - February 1968 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - April 1968 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - May 1968 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - June 1968 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - July 1968 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - September 1968 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - October 1968 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - November 1968 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - December 1968 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - January 1969, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - February 1969 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - March 1969 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - April 1969 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - June 1969 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - August 1969 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - October 1969 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - November 1969 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - December 1969 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - May-June 1970 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - July-August 1970 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - September 1970 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - October 1970 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - November-December 1970 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - January-March 1971 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - March-April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - June-August 1971 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - September-October 1971 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - November-December 1971 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - February-March 1972 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - April 1972 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Citizens Budget Committee Annual Dinner, Hotel Pierre, New York City, New York, May 1, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Dedication of the Eleanor Roosevelt Wing of the Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, Hyde Park, New York, May 3, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - NAR in Oregon, May 11, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Commonwealth Club, San Francisco, California, May 11, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Convention of the Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties, and Allied Products, Americana Hotel, New York City, May 16, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Center for Inter-American Relations, New York City, May 22, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Presentation Awards by NAR by the New York State Council of the Arts, Whitney Museum, New York, New York, May 25, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Presentation of John LaFarge Award to Senator Earl W. Brydges at the Catholic Interracial Council Dinner, New York City, May 25, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Interview of NAR by Albert Bobikov of TASS News Agency, New York, New York, May 26, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Swearing in of Stephen S. Gottlieb as a Member of the State Liquor Authority, New York, New York, May 26, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Swearing in of Frank S. Rossetti as Judge of the State Court of Claims, New York, New York, May 26, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Bill Signing of Environmental Improvement Bills, New York, New York, May 31, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Press Interview of NAR by William Farrell and Frank Lynn of the "New York Times," New York, New York, May 31, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 0122A)
    - Press Interview of NAR by Charles Dumas of the "New York Daily News," New York, New York, May 31, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 0122B)
    - Swearing-in Ceremonies of Miss Annie B. Martin, New York State Labor Department, Americana Hotel, New York, New York, May 31, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Remarks of NAR at a Rally for Chafee for Senator, Providence, Rhode Island, June 7, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Republican State Committee Luncheon, Hilton Hotel, New York, New York, June 8, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Republican State Committee Dinner, Hilton Hotel, New York, New York, June 8, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Meeting of New York State Historic Trust, Museum of Modern Art, New York, New York, June 13, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Wall Breaking Ceremony, Council of Jewish Women, Brooklyn, New York, June 13, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - NAR at the 1972 Safety Poster Contest Place Winners, New York City, June 14, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Press Questions of NAR by Jack Allen, WOR Radio News, New York City, June 14, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Remarks of NAR at Scholastic Achievement Dinner, New York City, June 14, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Joint News Conference with NAR and Shelby Seates, Seattle, Washington, June 15, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Pocantico Hills, Dinner, Congressman Peter Peysner, Pocantico, New York, June 18, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Remarks of NAR at the International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Union, Americana Hotel, New York, New York, June 19, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - News Conference of Whitney North Seymour, Jr., U. S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York, New York, New York, June 21, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Don Wickham Retirement Dinner, Thruway Hyatt House, Albany, New York, June 21, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Remarks of NAR at the New York State Republican Committee Luncheon, Thruway Hyatt House, Albany, New York, July 5, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Swearing in Ceremony of Martin Ginsberg as Judge, Family Court, Nassau County, New York, New York, July 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Interview of NAR by Gabe Pressman, WNEW-TV, New York, New York, July 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Remarks of NAR at the New York State Broadcasters Association 11th Annual Executive Conference, Hotel Otesaga, Cooperstown, New York, July 18, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Remarks of NAR at the John Peter Zenger Chapter of Sigma Delta Chi Meeting, White Plains College, White Plains, New York, July 19, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Art Interview by Paul Cummings of NAR, New York, New York, for the Archives of American Art, July 24, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Swearing in Ceremony of Italo Ablondi as Commissioner U. S. Tariff Commission, New York City, July 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - UDC Groundbreaking, Cathedral Parkway Houses, New York City (Cancelled), July 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Press Conference of NAR and Clark MacGregor, New York Committee to Re-Elect the President, New York City, July 26, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Interview of NAR by Bill Kennedy, New York City, July 27, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Press Conference at the King David Hotel, Israel, August 13, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Press Conference, NAR Returns from Israel at LaGuardia Airport, August 14, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Archer Avenue Groundbreaking Ceremony, Jamaica, New York, August 15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Endorsement of President Nixon's Re-elelction by Joint Council No. 16, Teamsters, New York, August 17, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, Concord Hotel, New York City, September 6, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Rally Honoring Commissioner Louis Levine, Flushing, New York, September 12, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Inaugural Luncheon of the Policemen's Benevolent Association, Tannersville, New York, September 14, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Joe Shannon Testimonial, White Plains Hotel, New York, September 15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 154)
    - Seventh Annual Gold Key Club Breakfast of Rockland County Republican Committee, Rockland County, New York, September 15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 155)
    - Press Conference of NAR Investigation of Corruption in Criminal Justice System on New York, New York, September 19, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 156)
    - Interview of NAR on Henry Kissinger by Bernard Kalb, New York City, September 19, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - NAR on the Martha Deane Show, WOR Radio, New York, September 20, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - Endorsement of President Richard Nixon by the Police Conference of New York, New York, September 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - Remarks of NAR at Ceremonies Marking Israel's 25th Anniversary, the International Synagogue, JFK Airport, New York, September 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 160)
    - Remarks of NAR at Press Conference Following Meeting of President Nixon and Labor Leaders Committee, Astoria Hotel, New York, September 27, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 161)
    - Remarks of NAR, Lt. Governor Malcolm Wilson and Commissioner Ewald B. Nyquist at the Presentation of Certificates Physicians Associates, New York, October 2, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 162)
    - Endorsement of President Richard M. Nixon by the Grand Council of Hispanic Societies in Public Service New York, October 4, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 163)
    - Remarks of NAR at Peter J. Brennan Testimonial Dinner, Hotel Commodore, New York, October 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 164)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Columbus Citizens Committee Annual Dinner at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York, October 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 165)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Eleventh Congress of Americans of Ukrainian Descent, Hotel Commodore, New York, October 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Remarks of NAR at the 36th Annual Pulaski Memorial Banquet at Statler-Hilton Hotel, New York, October 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Holing-Through Ceremony East 63rd Street Tunnel, Welfare Island, New York, October 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Rodney Square Rally for Peterson-Haskell, Wilmington, Delaware, October 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Senior Citizens Reception Held at Electra Arms, Wilmington, Delaware, October 10, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Student Assembly, Padua Academy, Wilmington, Delaware, October 10, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Press Conference, New York Democrats for Nixon, New York, October 11, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Workshop to Re-Elect the President, Roosevelt Hotel, New York City, October 11, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Cumberland County GOP Dinner at the Penn Harris Motor Inn, Pennsylvania, October 16, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Remarks of NAR in Support of Phil Hansen and Jon Haaven, Minnesota, October 17, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Travel Industry Committee to Re-Elect the President Dinner, New York City, Hilton, October 18, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Remarks of NAR at the New York State United Nations Day at Rockefeller Center, New York City, October 19, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Press Conference of New York Black Committee to Re-elect President Nixon, New York City, October 19, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Alfred E. Smith Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, October 19, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Remarks of NAR at Revenue Sharing Bill Signing Ceremony at Independence Hall, Pennsylvania, October 20, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Remarks of NAR at Second Avenue Subway Groundbreaking at 103rd Street and Second Avenue, New York City, October 27, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - Remarks of NAR at the National Press Club, Washignton, D. C., October 31, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Brotherhood-in-Action Dinner Honoring Senator Roy M. Goodman, Americana Hotel, New York City, October 31, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Press Conference: NAR and Jane Pickens Langley re: National Housing Program, New York City, November 1, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 184)
    - Press Conference NAR on Get Out the Vote Campaign, Re-elect the President, New York City, November 3, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 185)
    - Press Conference before the Statewide Swing to Get Out the Vote, LaGuardia Airport, New York, November 6, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 186)
    - Town Meeting Held at the Sheraton Syracuse Motor Inn, Syracuse, New York, November 13, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 187)
    - Elmira Town Meeting, Hickory House, Horseheads, New York, November 13, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Federation of Jewish Philanthropies Press Conference, Hotel Pierre, New York City, November 14, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - Oneida-Utica Town Meeting, Horizon Hotel, Oneida, New York, November 15, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - Olean Town Meeting, Castle Restaurant, Olean, New York, November 15, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 191)
    - Queens Town Meeting, JFK Airport, New York, November 17, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 192)
    - Interview of NAR by Valentin M. Berezhkov, Editor-in-Chief of U.S.A. (Moscow, U.S.S.R.), New York City, November 17, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Annual State Committee Meeting, Hotel Roosevelt, New York City, November 20, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 194)
    - Remarks of NAR at the Westchester County Association Dinner, Bill Butchner Testimonial, Schrafft's Restaurant, Eastchester, New York, November 21, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Lake Placid Town Meeting, New York, November 22, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Buffalo Town Meeting, New York, November 22, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - 78th National Conference on Government Innovations in State Fiscal Systems, Minneapolis, Minnesota, November 27, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - Stephen Rogers Award Dinner Anti-Defamation League, Syracuse, New York, November 29, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Rochester Town Meeting, New York, November 30, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Governor's Meeting with his Cabinet, Albany, New York, December 1, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Citations to National Guard Officers, Albany, New York, December 1, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Copernicus Award, New York City, December 6, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - Suffolk Town Meeting, Hauppauge, New York, December 11, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - Binghamton Town Meeting, New York, December 11, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Testimonial Dinner Senator Earl Brydges, Albany, New York, December 14, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - State Traffic Safety Council Luncheon, New York City, December 13, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 207)
    - News Conference State Capital, Albany, New York, December 15, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 208)
    - Luncheon, St. Regis Hotel, New York City, December 18, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 209)
    - Swearing-in Ceremonies Court of Appeals, Albany, New York, December 29, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 210)
    - Annual Message to the Legislature, Albany, New York, January 3, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 211)